

## **Personal Detail:**

Name	Shivam Singh	
Current Address	Gurgaon	
Martial Status	Single	
Permanent Adress	State- Uttar Pardesh	
	District- Ghazipur	

#### **SUMMARY:**

Presently working as Assistant Area Sales Manager in Asian Granito India Limited. Looked Gurgaon and Delhi Project. Worked Closely with all Stakeholder like Architects, Interior Designers, Builders, Purchase Head, Project Manager and Civil Contractor. I have 5 years of experience in Project Sales. I have completed my Graduation in Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA) from Marketing Specialization from Lovely Professional University. Highly motivated and Energetic person. Looking forward for new opportunity in any reputed Company where I Can use my Academic Knowledge and Sales Experience for Company Growth.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

## **Asian Granito India Limited:**

Assistant Area Sales Manager: From 26.10.2022 to Present.

#### **Job Responsblities:**

- Call Architects and take appointment for meeting.
- Meeting in Corporate Office with Architects, Contractor, Builder and Interior Designer for our Product Marble and Quartz.
- Responsible for Sales Growth of Marble and Quartz in our territory.
- Visit Client office at project and understand the current requirement and next requirement from Project Manager, Site Enginear and store Incharge.
- Providing sample of Marble and Quartz as per approved on project.
- Followup with customer for order.
- Visit Headoffice of Builder and meeting with Purchase Manager and provide him Quotation and close the deal.
- Ensure timely delivered of material at Project site by plant and dispatch team.
- Prepare and sending Monthly Sales report to Senior Area Sales Manager.

## Magicrete Building Solutions:

**Executive Sales & Marketing:** From 25.01.2021 to 18.10.2022. (1 Year 10 Month)

#### Job Responsiblities:

- Visit Project site and proper analysis the Site current stage, current stock and next requirement.
- Visit and meeting with Contractor's Project Manager and Store Incharge in the specified region regularly to understand current requirement and Monthly requirement of AAC Block at Project site.



- Visit Headoffice of Contractor and meeting with Purchase Manager and provide him Quotation and close the deal.
- Prepare and sending reports to the DGM and Maintaining quarterly and annually sales figure for the assigned territory.
- Take Order from party and place that order from Magicrete Mobile Application and get approved order from Finance team.
- Placed order and discuss with dispatch team and get material dispatched.
- Ensure timely delivered of material at Project site by plant and dispatch team.
- Follow-up with customers for overdue collection.
- Collect Cheque from party and ensure to payment received in company's account from Finance Team.

## Asian Paint:

Direct Sales Representative: From 17.01.2019 to 21.01.2021 (2 Years)

#### Job Responsbility

- Institutional sales of Paint, waterproofing and Adhesive through Builders, and Contractors.
- Responsible for sales growth of Paint, Waterproofing and Adhesive.
- Making monthly sales plan and achieve sales target.
- Placed ordered and ensured timely delivered of the product.
- Meeting conducted with Project Manager, Director, President of Society, Builder and Contractors.
- Visit at Institutional sites like Factory, Hospital, School and cooperative Housing Socitey for Paint and Waterproofing.
- Create Data of institutional sites, Client, Contractor and Builder.
- Send Paint, waterproofing, and texture Quotation to Client and contracter on their mail.
- Index Sites on Excel.
- Cold Calling.
- Follow-up at Hot Sites and Convert into business.
- Meeting with Dealer for lead.

# **Education** qualification

Serial no	Degree	Year	School/College
1	10th	2013	Brijnandani Convent school
2	12th	2015	NIOS
3	BBA (Marketing)	2018	Lovely Professional university

MS-Excel

## **Key Skills:**

Presentation Skill,
Negotion Skill,
Marketing skill,
MS-Word

Communication Skill in Hindi and English,

Self Motivated,



**Declaration:** I solemnly declare that above mention all the information are true and based of my knowledge.